<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PERFORMANCE-PRODUCT</string>
    <string name="Descripcion1">It is located 29 km from Bogotá, of which it is part of its area
         metropolitan, with a population of 126 4094 inhabitants, it is the second largest municipality and
         town of the province. It is one of the most important salt exploitation centers in Colombia,
         reason why it is also known as the Salt Capital of Colombia for its production of
         Salt.</string>
    <string name="Descripcion2">A soup made with chicken, potato and banana, and potatoes in brine, which are potatoes
         preserved in water with salt and sugar .</string>
    <string name="Descripcion3">Named First Wonder of Colombia in 2007. The cathedral is built
         in an underground salt mine and has several sculptures made with this mineral. Can be taken
         guided tours of the cathedral.</string>

    <string name="opcion1">Cundinamarca data</string>
    <string name="opcion2">Economy</string>
    <string name="opcion3">Spanish</string>
    <string name="opcion4">English</string>


    <string name="opcion1_subtitulo1">
        Data from the Department of Cundinamarca:
    </string>
    <string name="opcion1_descripcion1">
        Surface: 24.210 Km2.
        <br></br>
        Population: 2.721.368
        <br></br>
        Year of creation: 1886.
        <br></br>
        Demonym: Cundinamarqués
        <br></br>
        Capital: Santafé de Bogotá 8,314,305 inhabitants.
        <br></br>
        Main municipalities: La Vega, Girardot, Guaduas, Facatativa, Fusagasugá, Cáqueza,
        Zipaquirá, Ubaté, Villeta.
        <br></br>
        Limits: To the north with the departments of Boyacá and Meta; to the south with the departments of Meta,
        Huila and Tolima and to the west with the Magdalena River that separates it from the departments of
        Tolima and Caldas.
        <br></br>
        Physiography: The territory corresponds to the Eastern Cordillera that penetrates from the south
         forming the Páramo de Sumapaz; Its middle part presents the plateau of the Sabana de
         Bogota; and further north the valley of Ubaté and Simijaca. The flat and warm sectors of the
         department are the Magdalena valley and the part of the Eastern Plains.
        <br></br>
        Hydrography: Magdalena Guavio Suampuez, Humaca and Negro Rivers. Lagoons and dam; Guatavita,
         Chingaza, Fúquene, Neusa, Sisga, Chisacá, La Regadera and El Hato.
    </string>
    <string name="opcion2_subtitulo1">Economy</string>
    <string name="opcion2_descripcion1">
        The most outstanding natural resources are coal and salt, mainly in
         Zipaquirá, Nemocón and Tausa. It also has lime, iron, sulfur, emeralds, quartz,
         lead, plaster, copper and marble.
        <br></br>
        The main agricultural products are coffee, corn, sugar cane, potato, barley, wheat,
         cassava, cotton, rice, beans and fruits, the department is the first producer of sugarcane
         panelera sugar of the country. The dairy is highly developed especially in the Savannah
         from Bogotá and in the valley of Ubaté.
    </string>

</resources>